Introduction:
The first motor-driven expansion board based on ESP-12E.
Features:
ESP12 DEV KIT development board expansion module;
Derive all function pins of ESP12 DEV KIT: SPI, UART, GPIO, AI and 3.3V power interface;
Expand two-way motor drive, can directly drive two-way motor;
Onboard power switch;
L293D
Motor power range: 4.5V~36V;
Control power range: 4.5V~9V;
Motor power and control power are separated. In the experiment, VIN and VM can be short-circuited by short-circuiting blocks, and the motor and the control board can be powered at the same time.
 
Product specifications
Power input:
Motor power supply (VM): 4.5V ~ 36V, can be individually powered;
Control power (VIN): 4.5V ~ 9V (10VMAX), can be independently powered;
The module provides short-circuits (short-circuit VM and VIN). It is convenient to use one-way power (4.5V~9V) to complete the motor drive and control at the same time.
Logic operating current Iss: ≤ 60mA (Vi = L), ≤ 22mA (Vi = H);
Drive part of the operating current Io: ≤ 1.2A;
Maximum Dissipation Power: 4W (T=90°C)
Control signal input level: high level: 2.3V≤VIH≤VIN; low level: -0.3V≤VIL≤1.5V
Working temperature: -25°C～+125°C
Drive form: Dual high-power H-bridge drive
ESP12E Dev Kit control port: D1, D3 (A motor); D2, D4 (B motor)
Module weight: about 20g
 
Precautions
When inserting the ESP-12E module, please note that the direction of the antenna is consistent with that of the expansion board.
With the shorting module, power can be supplied to the control board and the motor at the same time.
 
Package list :1X L293D ESP8266 ESP-12E Expansion board